When life keeps you apart, fight for every inch.
Five Feet Apart is a romance, drama film directed by Justin Baldoni.
Seventeen-year-old Stella spends most of her time in the
hospital as a cystic fibrosis patient.
Her life is full of routines, boundaries and self-control — all of which get put to the test
when she meets Will, an impossibly charming teen who has the same illness.
There's an instant flirtation, though restrictions dictate that
they must maintain a safe distance between them.
As their connection intensifies, so does the temptation to throw the
rules out the window and embrace that attraction.
Stella Grant, played by Haley Lu Richardson.
Will Newman, played by Cole Sprouse.
Poe Ramírez, played by Moisés Arias.
Barbara, played by Kimberly Hébert Gregory.
Dr. Noor Hamid, played by Parminder Nagra.
Meredith Newman, played by Claire Forlani.
Five Feet Apart is a 2019 American coming-of-age romantic drama film directed by Justin Baldoni
(in his directorial debut) and written by Mikki Daughtry and Tobias Iaconis.
The film was inspired by Claire Wineland, who had cystic fibrosis.
Haley Lu Richardson and Cole Sprouse play two young patients with cystic fibrosis who try to
have a relationship despite being forced to stay five feet apart from each other.
The film was released in the United States on March
15, 2019, by CBS Films via Lionsgate.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $92 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of forbidden love, terminal
illness, hospital, best friend, falling in love.
The tone is emotional.